justonedime.com 2019-01-22

# Privacy Policy

_Last updated: October 12, 2018_

At Just One Dime, Inc. (“we,” “us” or “Just One Dime”), we respect and protect the privacy of visitors to our website, www.justonedime.com, and the other websites under the justonedime.com domain (collectively, the "Sites"), and any products or services made available from time to time by means of any of the Sites (the “Products”). We refer to the Sites and the Products collectively in this Privacy Policy as the “Services.”

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy” or "Policy") explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect visitors’ and users’ information as part of the Service. Any discussion of your use of the Service in this Policy is meant to include your visits and other interactions with the Sites and Services, whether or not you are a member of any of Just One Dime's memberships or services.

Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Service.

By accessing and using our Service, you signify your acceptance to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with or you are not comfortable with any aspect of this Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue access or use of our Services.

### 1\. What "Personal Information" means

In this Policy, “Personal Information” means information or an information set that identifies or could be used to identify an individual directly or indirectly. Except as described in this Policy, Just One Dime will not give, sell, rent, or loan any Personal Information to any third party.

Personal Information does not include “Usage Data” which we define as encoded or anonymized information or aggregated data we collect about a group or category of services, features, or users which does not contain personally identifying information. Usage Data helps us understand trends in usage of the Service so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor the Service. In addition to collecting and using Usage Data ourselves, we may share Usage Data with third parties, including our customers, partners and service providers, for various purposes, including to help us better understand our customers’ needs and improve the Service as well as for advertising and marketing purposes.

### 2\. How we collect, use, and share your Personal Information and other information

Some of the information we collect when you use the Services, such as your name, postal address, email address, credit card information, or telephone number, may allow you to be identified (“Personal Information”). In all of the following circumstances, we will use Personal Information for the purpose described below, as well as to supplement our database of marketing contacts, which we will use to provide and promote products and services from us or our marketing affiliates.

#### a. Information you provide to us

When you register for the Service, we may ask for Personal Information such as your name, email address, or credit card or other billing information. You may also provide at your own discretion certain related information like your personal website name, social media websites, a list of your skills, the date you started using the Service, and a description of yourself. Additionally, as you use the service via the member portal, the software will document items such as when you access different pages, sections of the member portal, or when you perform certain tasks.

We may also retain the contents of any messages you send to us or through the Service, and we may collect information you provide in user content that you post or upload to the Service (“User Content”).

Just One Dime may use Personal Information provided to operate, improve upon, and personalize the Service, for billing identification and authentication, to contact and communicate with you about the Service and your use of the Service, to support use of the Service, to send marketing materials for research purposes, and to generally improve the content and functionality of the Service.

We may also combine your Personal Information with third-party analytics information to build a broader profile of our individual users so that we can serve you better and provide custom, personalized content and information. Additionally, we may use the Personal Information we collect for identification and authentication and fraud prevention, to analyze Site usage and improve the Service, for internal market research, troubleshooting problems, to enforce our Terms of Service, and as otherwise set forth in this Policy.

Note that we will never email you to ask for your account information. If you ever receive such an email, please forward it to [hello@justonedime.com](mailto:hello@justonedime.com). For more information about our procedures in this regard, please review our Terms of Service.

We use financial information solely as authorized by you in accordance with the Service. While Just One Dime does not store your credit card information and will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of all credit card and all other Personal Information, we expressly disclaim any liability for any unauthorized access to or use of our secure servers and/or any and all personal and/or financial information stored therein, and you agree to hold Just One Dime harmless for any damages that may result therefrom.

#### b. Information we may receive from and share with third parties

We may now or in the future receive Personal Information about you from third parties. For example, we may allow a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Site. If we do so, this company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to the Services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to the Services, the advertiser might place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Information we may share with third parties could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account, an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that third-party service.

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;
  * When you participate in the interactive areas of our Services, certain information you provide may be displayed to other users, such as your name, photo, comments and other information you choose to provide;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Company or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

We may offer you the opportunity to contact other companies, such as advertisers, marketing affiliates and content providers, to obtain information or to buy products or services. You decide when and whether to give your Personal Information to these companies. If you provide information, its use and security is governed by the policies and practices of those companies and not by this privacy policy.

We make no representations or warranties about any of these other companies or their privacy or security policies. Once you click through to an unaffiliated website, this privacy policy no longer applies. We strongly urge you to read the applicable policies of these other companies and their websites.

#### c. Analytics information

We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including the web pages you visit, your browser add-ons, and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We may collect and use this analytics information together with your Personal Information to build a broader profile of our individual users so that we can serve you better.

The Site primarily uses the following analytical tools, for which we include relevant privacy information and opt-out options:

##### Google Analytics and Google Adwords

Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Service](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms) and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You may also [learn more about how Google collects and processes data](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) specifically in connection with Google Analytics. You may prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics by downloading and installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

##### Facebook Remarketing Service

Facebook’s use of information collected is set forth in its [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation). You may [opt out from Facebook’s interest-based ads](https://www.facebook.com/about/ads/).

##### Visual Website Optimizer (VWO)

VWO's use of information collected is set forth in its [Privacy Policy.](https://vwo.com/privacy-policy/) You may opt out from VWO's tracking [here.](https://justonedime.com/?vwo_opt_out=1)

#### d. Blog and forums

We may provide an opportunity for you to post information to blogs, forums or other public areas on the Services. By doing so, you consent to the posting of any Personal Information that you provide. You should be aware that such Personal Information can be read, collected, or used by other visitors to these public areas. We have no control over how these visitors use your Personal Information.

If you remove information that you posted to the Service, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of the Service, or if other users have copied or saved that information. To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [hello@justonedime.com](mailto:hello@justonedime.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove all your Personal Information.

#### e. Inquiries

If you send us a comment or question or make an inquiry to customer support, we will retain the information that you provide to us for the purpose of responding to you, as well as for improving the Services and our customers’ use of our services.

#### f. Linking from emails

If you link to any of our Sites from an email message from us, we will be able to identify your email address and associate that email address with the manner in which you use the Sites (e.g., which pages you visit or whether you make a purchase).

#### g. Visitors

If you are just visiting the Sites and not registering, requesting information, contacting us, or posting to a public area of the Services, and you did not access the Sites from a link contained in one of our email communications, we will not ordinarily collect any Personal Information about you except through web logs, as described below. In that case, we obtain the information that you provided and will use it to respond to your inquiry or fulfill your request if we can. We do not share any of this information with anyone else, except to respond to your request, if you consent, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

#### h. Web logs

We maintain web logs that automatically record basic information about everyone who visits the Services. We use web log information to help us design our website, identify popular features, improve our services, and for other managerial and analytic purposes. We may also use web logs to help identify any person who may be misusing the Services. These logs contain:

  * The Internet domain from which you access the Services 
  * Your IP address
  * The type of browser and operating system that you use
  * The date and time you visited the Services
  * The pages that you visited on the Services
  * The address of the website you linked from to get to the Services

Occasionally, we may connect Personal Information to information gathered in our log files, as necessary to improve the Service for individual customers. Otherwise, we generally use this information as we would any Usage Data, to analyze trends, administer and maintain the Service, or track usage of various features within the Service.

#### i. Cookies

A cookie is a small software file stored temporarily or placed on your computer’s hard drive. The main purpose of cookie is to allow a web server to identify a user’s computer and web browser, and tailor web pages and/or login information to user’s preferences. Cookies help us promptly display the information needed to use the capabilities on the Service and other information which we consider to be of interest to visitors to the Sites and users of the Service. By gathering and remembering information about website preferences through cookies, we can provide a better web and marketing experience. Cookies don’t give us access to users’ computers, and the information we collect through cookies doesn’t include Personal Information.

We utilize session cookies, which allow us to uniquely identify your browser while you are logged in and to process your online transactions. Session cookies disappear from your computer when the web browser is closed or computer is turned off. We also utilize persistent cookies to make it easier to log into and use the Service. Persistent cookies remain on computers after the web browser is closed or the computer is turned off.

Many jurisdictions require or recommend that website operators inform users as to the nature of cookies they utilize and, in certain circumstances, obtain the consent of their users to the placement of certain cookies. If you require more specific information as to the nature of the cookies utilized in the Service for purposes of fulfilling these obligations, please contact us by email at [hello@justonedime.com](mailto:hello@justonedime.com).

#### j. Communicating with you

We may use information that we collect from you for the purpose of communicating with you and responding to your inquiries. Those communications could, for example, take the form of service updates, promotions for products or services that we or one of our marketing partners provide, or e-newsletters.

#### k. Service providers

We at times contract with third party service providers to perform functions for us. These service providers may be given access to the information we collect for the purpose of performing those functions, but they will be contractually bound to maintain the confidentiality of the information and not to use it for any other purpose.

#### l. Social media

The Sites may include social media features, such as Facebook “Like” button and a “Share” button. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on the Site; and they may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company that provides the feature. Business Transfers: If we were to transfer all or substantially all of our assets to another company, one of the assets we would likely include in the transfer is our database of Personal Information.

#### j. Do not track

There will be no difference in how we collect or use data if you set your web browser to send a “Do not track” or similar request when you visit this Site.

#### m. Other information sharing

We may be required to disclose Personal Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and law enforcement or governmental requests or investigations, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations or our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

We may share Personal Information with any member of the Just One Dime team, which includes any entity that controls, is controlled by, or under common control with Just One Dime.

### 3\. Links to other websites

The Service contains links to websites and applications other than the Service, including websites and applications operated by affiliates and other third parties. This Policy applies only to information collected by the Service.

Just One Dime does not endorse and is not responsible for the practices of third parties or their websites or applications. We do not determine and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites or applications operated by third parties. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies.

We are not responsible for and we do not control any third parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service and you allow such a third-party access to your User Content, you do so at your own risk.

### 4\. Use of information

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * Remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site
  * Provide, maintain, improve and promote our products and services;
  * Provide and deliver the information, products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and receipts;
  * Help you efficiently access your information after you sign in;
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests, and provide customer service;
  * Communicate with you about products, services, surveys, offers, promotions, rewards and events offered by Company and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, metrics, usage, and activities in connection with our Services, such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns;
  * Diagnose or fix technology problems;
  * Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests;
  * Automatically update the Just One Dime application on your mobile devices;
  * Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions, and process and deliver entries and rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries. Furthermore, when you sign up for our products, you are agreeing to our storage of your information on a server maintained in the United States. By purchasing our products and providing information, you are consenting to our terms of use, which are governed by laws of the United States.

### 5\. Customer testimonials / comments / reviews

From time to time, we post customer testimonials on the Sites which may contain Personal Information. We always obtain the customers’ consent prior to posting their names along with their testimonials.

### 6\. Protection of information

Just One Dime is committed to ensuring the security of your Personal Information. We use commercially reasonable technological, physical, and administrative security safeguards, such as firewalls and carefully developed security features, to protect the confidentiality and security of your Personal Information within the Service and the Sites. When you enter confidential information (such as login credentials or information submitted from within the Service) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). These technologies, procedures, and other measures are used in an effort to ensure that your data is safe, secure, and only available to you and to those you authorized to access your data. However, no internet, email, or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error-free, so you should take care in deciding what information you send to us in this way. Just One Dime is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

### 7\. Your privacy choices

We process and store information on behalf of our customers. You may decline to submit any Personal Information through the Service, in which case we may not be able to provide certain services to you. If you would like us to stop sending you email or other communications or would like to access your Personal Information to correct or delete it, you may send us a request at [hello@justonedime.com](mailto:hello@justonedime.com) or our postal address indicated below. We will endeavor to satisfy such requests within a reasonable time.

#### a. Your information

You may review, correct or modify information maintained in your online account at any time by logging into your account and updating your profile information or by emailing us at [hello@justonedime.com](mailto:hello@justonedime.com). If you wish to delete or deactivate your account, please email us at [hello@justonedime.com](mailto:hello@justonedime.com), but note that some information you provide through the products may continue to be accessible (e.g., comments you submit through the Services) and that we may continue to store information about you as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

#### b. Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Note that disabling cookies on your mobile device or browser may prevent us or our business partners from tracking your browser’s activities in relation to the Service. However, doing so may disable many of the features available through the Service.

#### c. Promotional communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the instructions in those communications or by sending an email to [hello@justonedime.com](mailto:hello@justonedime.com). If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations. You may also opt-out individually for third-party vendors on their websites, but limitations on data sharing may make it difficult or impossible to provide the Service after an opt-out

### 8\. Data retention

Just One Dime will retain Personal Information we process on behalf of our customers or collect directly from our customers for as long as needed to provide Service to our customers, subject to our compliance with this Policy, or as required or permitted under the applicable law. We may further retain and use this Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations; maintain accurate accounting, financial, and other operational records; resolve disputes; and enforce our agreements. We have established internal policies for the deletion of data from customer accounts following termination of a customer’s subscription to the Service.

### 9\. Children's personal information

This Site is intended for use by adults. Just One Dime does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. **If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Information through our Service.** We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s internet usage and to help enforce our Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information on our Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to Just One Dime through our Service, please contact us, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information from our databases.

### 10\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may, in our sole discretion, modify or update this Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Policy, we will endeavor to notify you by email or by posting a prominent notice on the Sites prior to the change becoming effective but will not be liable for any failure to do so. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes to this Policy. Your only remedy, if you do not accept the terms of this Policy, is to discontinue use of the Service.

### 11\. Business transactions

Just One Dime may assign or transfer this Policy, and your user account and related Personal Information, to any person or entity that acquires all or substantially all of the business, stock or assets of, or is merged with Just One Dime. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies, dissolutions, or similar transactions or proceedings, provided that the recipient of such information will continue to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### 12\. Contact us

We are committed to adhering to our privacy policy and applicable laws and to making your online experience secure and valuable. If you have a question, request, complaint, dispute, or concern related to this Privacy Policy or about the privacy practices of Just One Dime, you may contact us by email at [hello@justonedime.com](mailto:hello@justonedime.com), or at:

Just One Dime, Inc.  
PO Box 1123,  
Pflugerville, TX 78691\. 

We will work with you to obtain a prompt resolution of any issues you may have.
